另一方面呢  物理学家又开始担心
On the other hand, some physicists are concerned
一旦超撞机真的实现
That if this supercollider actually works,
它产生的黑洞会吞噬地球
It'll create a black hole and swallow up the earth,
终结生命
Ending life as we know it.
真是一群爱哭鬼
Pfft, what a bunch of crybabies.
人有多大胆  地有多大产
No guts, no glory, man.
嘿  看看这个
Hey, check it out.
药学院要招志愿者
The school of pharmacology is looking for volunteers.
"我们正在测试一种新药  专治社交焦虑症
"we are testing a new medication "for social anxiety, panic attacks,
恐慌发作症  陌生环境恐怖症和强迫症"
Agoraphobia and obsessive compulsive disorder."
他们为什么要在这招人?
Why would they be looking for test subjects here?
我怎么知道  拉杰
I don't know, raj.
没准是因为漫画书店没有布告栏
Maybe the comic book store doesn't have a bulletin board.
在这干什么呢?
What's going on?
嘘  嘘  谢尔顿办公室有个靓妹
Shh, shh, hot girl in sheldon's office.
在谢尔顿的办公室?
Sheldon's office?
她是不是走丢了?
Is she lost?
我认为不是
I don't think so.
我从停车场就开始跟着她了
I followed her here from the parking lot.
可能她是他的律师
Maybe she's his lawyer.
那她可以随时查看我的诉讼
Well, she's free to examine my briefs.
-霍华德  -我知道  我很恶心
Howard. I know, I'm disgusting.
我应该被惩罚...被她惩罚
I should be punished... by her.
看  我还是这么恶心
Oh, look, I did it again.
那样就差不多了
That should do it.
麻烦你跑一趟
Thank you for coming by.
你们好啊
Hello.
嘿  老弟...
Oh, hey, buddy...
"老弟..."?
"buddy..."?
不好意思  我来迟了
Sorry I'm late.
我正在攻关一个项目  可能要上下一次航天飞机了
I'm working on a project that may take me up on the next space shuttle.
为什么要说晚了呢?
How can you be late?
我根本没想要你来
I wasn't expecting you at all.
我总是神出鬼没
Nobody ever expects me.
有时你只是看着看着就...
Sometimes you just look and...
霍华德·沃尔维茨驾到
Bam! howard wolowitz.
谢尔顿  能介绍一下吗?
Sheldon, are you gonna introduce us?
可以  这是米茜
Oh, all right. uh, this is missy.
米茜  这是里奥纳德和拉杰  你已经见过霍华德了
Missy, this is leonard and rajesh, and you've already met howard.
很高兴见到你们
It's nice to meet you.
你也是  也  也是
You, too, as well, also.
是
Yeah.
你们两个是怎么认识的?
So, how do you two know each other?
他的头可在我的胯下呆过9个月
Oh, he once spent nine months with my legs wrapped around his head.
啊?
Excuse me?
她是我的孪生妹妹
She's my twin sister.
她以为自己很风趣  但说实话  我从来看不出
She thinks she's funny, but frankly, I've never been able to see it.
这是因为你根本无法衡量什么是幽默  谢利(昵称)
That's because you have no measurable sense of humor, shelly.
一个人要怎么衡量幽默?
How exactly would one measure a sense of humor?
幽默测量器?
A humormometer?
我觉得你非常得幽默
Well, I think you're delightfully droll.
-当然  就像法语中  "你真有趣"  -看我记不记得住
Ooor, as the french say, tres drole. okay, so let me see if I got this.
里奥纳德  霍华德  还有...
Leonard, howard and...
不好意思  你叫?
I'm sorry, what was your name again?
拉杰
Rajesh.
天才也性感 第一季 第15集
The Big Bang Theory S01E15
那么  米茜  你为什么从德州跑到这来?
So, missy, what brings you all the way from texas?
是不是缘分?  我觉得是缘分
Was it perhaps destiny? I think it was destiny.
我朋友明晚在迪斯尼结婚
My friend's s getting married at disneyland tomorrow night.
缘分  名字就叫做阿纳海姆市(美国南加州)
Destiny, thy name is anaheim.
我还过来让谢利在父亲的地产文书上签个字
And I had to drop off some papers for shelly to sign for my dad's estate.
文书可以邮寄的吧
The papers could've been mailed.
妈让你来监视我  没错吧
Mom just sent you here to spy on me, didn't she?
我想这就是为什么他们要管你叫天才了
I guess that's why they call you a genius.
他们叫我天才是因为我确实是天才
They call me a genius because I'm a genius.
告诉妈我目前165磅
Tell mom that I currently weigh 165 pounds
还有我的胃肠蠕动正常
And that I'm having regular bowel movements.
好好享受婚礼  拜拜
Enjoy the wedding. good-bye.
婚礼不是明天吗  不如你今晚来我们这吧?
If the wedding's not until tomorrow, why don't you stay with us tonight?
我看行不通
Oh, I don't think so.
谢利不喜欢别人缠着他
Shelly doesn't like company.
即使是在他小时候
Even as a little boy,
他也会在晚上把假想的朋友送回家
He'd send his imaginary friends home at the end of the day.
他们不是朋友
They were not friends.
他们是假想的同事
They were imaginary colleagues.
你看  你都来了
Look, you're here.
我们有很多房间的
We have plenty of room.
不  我们没有
No, we don't.
别这样  谢利  她是家人啊
Come on, shelly. she's family.
那又怎么样  我都没有邀请你妈来
So what, I don't issue invitations to your mother.
能不用在高峰时段开去阿纳海姆也不错啊
Well, it would be nice not to have to drive to anaheim in rush hour.
再也不要叫我谢利
And don't ever call me shelly.
就这么定了  你住我们这儿
So it's settled. You'll stay with us.
我带你去拿车
Yeah, I'll walk you to your car.
你车停在3区  c层  没错吧
You're in structure 3, level c, right?
这都是怎么一回事?
What just happened?
反正
So anyway,
我们8岁时  谢尔顿把我的
We're eight years old and sheldon converts my
傻瓜式烤箱改装成了一种高能量熔炉
Easy bake oven to some kind of high-powered furnace.
太经典了
Just classic.
我要做家用集成电路
I needed a place to fire ceramic
需要一个可以融化半导体陶瓷基底的地方
Semiconductor substrates for homemade integrated circuits.
他当时想要造一个
He was trying to build some sort of
武装机器人来把我赶出他的房间
Armed robot to keep me out of his room.
要不是你一直闯进我的房间这也没必要
Made necessary by her insistence on going into my room.
还有  我去做了些小的玉米蛋糕
Anyway, I go to make those little corn muffins they give you.
突然哗的一下
There's a big flash.
你醒来的时候眉毛就不见了
Next thing you know my eyebrows are gone.
你的眉毛?
Not your eyebrows.
然后我整个二年级都要
I had to go through the entire second
顶着妈妈画的弯曲的假眉毛去上学
Grade with crooked eyebrows my mom drew on.
是这样吗?
Is that what that was?
我还以为是二年级的课程
I just assumed that the second grade
让你行为变得有些古怪
Curriculum had rendered you quizzical.
里奥纳德  你短裤忘在楼下的干衣机里了
Hey, leonard, you left your underwear in the dryer downstairs.
那不是我的
Those are not mine.
真的吗
Really?
这里面有你名字的小标签啊
They have your little name label in them.
对...不  我...
Yeah... no, I do... i...
我是用这来磨光我捕鱼用的鱼叉器材的
I use those, uh, just to polish up my spearfishing equipment.
我用鱼叉捕鱼的
I spearfish.
我不去用石弓打猎时  我会去用鱼叉捕鱼
When I'm not crossbow hunting, I spearfish.
潘妮  这是谢尔顿的孪生妹妹  米茜
Uh, penny, this is sheldon's twin sister, missy.
-米茜  这是我们的邻居潘妮  -你们看起来长得不像啊
Missy, this is our neighbor penny. don't look that much alike.
让我说声哈利路亚(赞美上帝)
Can I get a hallelujah?
异卵双生的双胞胎来自于两个不同的卵子中
Fraternal twins come from two separate eggs.
他们不像一般的同胞手足那样
They are no more alike than any other siblings.
哈利路亚!
Hallelujah!
你们知道不
Hey, guess what.
我已经被接受做为试验体了
I've been accepted as a test subject for a
测试一种治疗病态羞怯症的神奇新药
New miracle drug to overcome pathological shyness.
那太好了  拉杰
Oh, good for you, raj.
是  我有希望了  你好  米茜
Yes, I'm very hopeful. hello, missy.
他们提到过可能会有副作用
They mentioned there may be side effects.
米茜  你遇到过来自充满异域风情的印度次大陆的男人吗
So, missy, have you ever met a man from the exotic subcontinent of india?
有  我们教堂的帕特尔医生
Well, there's dr. patel at our church.
没错  帕特尔  他人不错
Ah, yes, patel-- good man.
你喜欢摩托车吗
Do you like motorcycles?
我有一台哈雷摩托(俚语指小弟弟)
'cause I ride a hog.
哈雷?
A hog?
你那辆是两轮的踏板车  前面还装个小篮子的
You have a two-cylinder scooter with a basket in the front.
你一样得带头盔吧
You still have to wear a helmet.
你听说过伽摩经吗
Have you ever heard of the kama sutra?
讲性爱的书
The sex book.
是印度的性爱之书
The indian sex book.
换句话说  如果你好奇是谁写了这本关于爱的书
In other words, if you "wonder, wonder who wrote the book of love,
是我们印度人
" it was us.
谢尔顿的妹妹挺漂亮啊  是吧
So, sheldon's sister is pretty cute, huh?
我没有盯着她看
I wasn't staring.
我没有说你在盯着她啊  我只是说她挺漂亮
I didn't say you were. I just said she was cute.
可能吧  如果你喜欢这么高...
Oh, eh... maybe, if you like women who are tall...
而且完美的
And perfect.
谢尔顿  你怎么不理你妹妹啊
Sheldon, why are you ignoring your sister?
我没有不理我妹妹  我是不理你们任何人
I'm not ignoring my sister. I'm ignoring all of you.
这里有些小吃
I brought snacks!
哈  腌黄瓜和..
Oh, my, gherkins and...
洋葱酱  这个是洋葱酱
Onion dip. it's onion dip.
我们不常招待人的
We don't entertain much.
米茜
Missy.
你喜欢穿睡衣吗
Do you enjoy pajamas?
应该是吧
I guess.
太好了  是我们印度人发明的睡衣
Yeah, we indians invented them.
不客气
You're welcome.
那这么说  是我们犹太人发明了割礼
Yeah, well, my people invented circumcision.
不客气
You're welcome.
米茜  我要去做指甲
Missy, I'm gonna go get my nails done.
想一起去吗
Do you want to come?
太好了  我去  谢谢你
God, yes. thanks.
不客气
You're welcome.
-大伙再见  -再见  米茜
Bye, guys. bye, missy.
-米茜  再见  -再见  里奥纳德
Bye, missy, see you. good-bye, leonard.
对...不...再见  潘妮
Oh, yeah, no, uh, bye, penny.
听着  你们俩给我闪开
Okay, you two have to back off.
我干吗要闪开  你闪开  伙计
Why should I back off? you back off, dude.
不好意思  这是我的房子  她是我室友的妹妹
Excuse me, this is my apartment, and she's my roommate's sister.
那又怎么样  你已经有潘妮了
So what? you've already got penny!
我怎么有潘妮了?
How do I have penny?
我到底哪门子有潘妮了?
In what universe do I have penny?
那我可以追她了?
So I can have penny?
该死  不行!
Hell, no!
抱歉  我能插两句吗
Excuse me. can I interject something?
我正在线订一个披萨
I'm ordering pizza online.
意大利辣香肠你们都吃吧?
Is everyone okay with pepperoni?
谢尔顿  我能跟你单独谈一下吗
Sheldon, can I talk to you in private?
行啊
I guess.
别担心  我会点那种芝士少一点的
Don't worry. I was going to order you cheese-less.
-谢谢你  -没事
Thank you. it's okay.
不能吃乳糖不是什么丢脸的事
Lactose intolerance is nothing to be embarrassed about.
我是梦幻印度情人
I'm a fancy indian man.
我们发明了睡衣
We invented pajamas.
看我  我没有包皮
Hey, look at me. I don't have a foreskin.
谢尔顿...
Sheldon...
你难道没意识到你妹妹魅不可挡吗
Are you aware that your sister is an incredibly attractive woman?
她确实有着西方文化所青睐的
She certainly has the symmetry and low
既匀称而又低脂肪的身段
Body fat that western culture deems desirable.
这倒是值得注意的  在历史上
It's noteworthy, at other points in history,
胖一些的女人象征着美丽
Heavier women were the standard for
因为她们的腰身意味着富饶
Beauty because their girth suggested affluence.
很令人着迷  但...
That's fascinating, but...
我没有说令人着迷  我只是说值得注意
I didn't say it was fascinating. I said it was noteworthy.
好吧  我注意到了
All right... noted.
我的意思是  库萨帕里和沃尔维茨
But my point is that koothrappali and wolowitz,
他们在泡你的妹妹啊
They're hitting on your sister.
这简直...
Oh, it's...
没事啊
Oh, okay.
我不想评价你说话的修辞手法
You know, I don't want to criticize your rhetorical style,
但要是你能开门见山地说
But we'd be a lot further along in this
我们可能已经谈得很深了
Conversation if you'd begun with that thought.
-很好  -但是...
That's great, but my...
我要说的是  我们拐了个不必要的弯
What I'm saying is that we took quite an Unnecessary detour
因为现在我发现这才是你的论点
from what I now understand to be your thesis.
又怎么了
Whatever.
你不能干坐着啊
You have to do something about it.
为什么
Why?
因为她是你妹妹
Because she's your sister.
我不明白
I don't understand.
不错  我们共同在一个子宫里待过九个月
Yes, we shared a uterus for nine months,
但此后我们就你走阳关道我走独木桥了
But since then we've pretty much gone our own separate ways.
好吧  那这么想吧...
Okay, uh, consider this...
你父亲去世之后
With your father gone,
确保米茜能选择一位合适的伴侣就是你的责任了
It is your responsibility to make sure that missy chooses a suitable mate.
我倒没想过这个
I hadn't considered that.
我们确实有相同的DNA
We do share dna. uh-huh.
所以有这种可能  尽管可能性不大
So there is the possibility, however remote,
她的天赋可以创造另一个
That resting in her loins is the potential
像我这样不平凡的人
For another individual as remarkable as myself.
正是
Exactly.
并且你有责任替你自己和你子孙保留
And you owe it to yourself and to posterity to protect
你妹妹所传后代遗传基因的完整性
The genetic integrity of your sister's future offspring.
你说的对
You're right.
如果有人想接近米茜的输卵管
If someone wants to get at missy's fallopian tubes,
他们必须通过我
They'll have to go through me.
我是摧毁者西瓦(游戏"怒之铁拳"中的BOSS)
I am shiva the destroyer!
我会赢得这个女人
I will have the woman.
警告你  我可是数学夏令营的柔道冠军
I'm warning you I was judo champion at math camp.
好了  你们幼稚够了吧
All right, now that's enough juvenile squabbling.
给我停下
You stop it.
我说给我停下!
Stop it, I say!
我现在就来处理这件事
I'm going to settle this right now.
你们中的任何一个都配不上我妹妹
Neither of you are good enough for my sister.
你是谁  凭什么你决定?
Who are you to decide that?
他是这个家的男人
He's the man of his family.
你们必须尊重他的意愿
You have to respect his wishes.
-顺便说一句  你也出局了  -你说什么?
You're out, too, by the way. say what?
我不是针对你
It's nothing personal.
我只是更希望我将来的侄子或者侄女
I'd just prefer if my future niece or nephew
不要成为那种每次吃到爱斯基摩派就会欢呼雀跃的人
Didn't become flatulent every time they ate an eskimo pie.
你高兴个什么劲儿
What are you so happy about?
我不是高兴
I'm not happy.
药起作用了  我停不下来
It's the medication. I can't stop smiling.
里奥纳德让我意识到遗传基因的赌注有多大
That leonard's made me aware of how high the genetic stakes are,
我们必须面对现实
We have to face the fact that none
你们没有一个配得上我妹妹
Of you are suitable mates for my sister.
等一下
Wait a minute.
是里奥纳德让你意识到的?
Leonard made you aware of that?
我们都会犯错  换个话题吧
We all make mistakes. let's move on.
插一句  不过我认为你错失了一个良机
Excuse me, but I think you're missing a big opportunity here.
怎么说
How so?
每个人都知道基因多样化能创造出了不起的后代
Everybody knows genetic diversity produces the strongest offspring.
不如考虑在家庭的拿铁咖啡里放点穆哈调和一下
Why not put a little mocha in the family latte?
理论上  你说的没错
In principle, you have a point.
但考虑到实际情况
But as a practical matter,
允许我提醒你一下  你都需要实验性药品
Need I remind you that it takes experimental
才能让你更容易开口跟异性说话
Pharmaceuticals to simply enable you to speak to the opposite sex.
我觉得你把太多的焦点放在药物上了
I think you're focusing entirely too much on the drugs.
是不是因为我是个犹太人?
Is it 'cause I'm jewish?
要知道为了和你妹妹在一起  我愿意用猪排杀了我的导师
'cause I'd kill my rabbi with a pork chop to be with your sister.
这和你的宗教信仰无关
This has nothing to do with religion.
只是因为你还是个小男孩
This has to do with the fact that you're a tiny,
一个仍和妈妈一起住的小男孩
Tiny man who still lives with his mother.
谢尔顿  你真不讲道理
Sheldon, you are really being unreasonable.
是吗
Am i?
来  吃了这片芝士能不放屁  你就可以和我妹上床
Here, eat this cheese without farting and you can sleep with my sister.
噢  真的吗
Oh, really?
靠
Oops.
谢利  我可以和你说几句吗
Shelly, can I speak to you for a minute?
私下里
Alone.
为什么大家突然都想和我单独谈话
Why does everyone suddenly want to talk to me alone?
通常没有人喜欢和我单独相处的呀
Usually nobody wants to be alone with me.
我们都会犯错  换一个话题吧
We all make mistakes. let's move on.
好吧  我不想过问你为何为了区区芝士把我推销出去
Okay, I'm not even going to ask why you're pimping me out for cheese.
不过你何时开始关心我和谁上床了?
But since when do you care at all about who I sleep with?
说实话  我从来没有考虑过
Well, truthfully, I've never given it any thought,
不过我后来意识到  你身上带着潜在的DNA
But it has been pointed out to me that you carry dna of great potential.
你在说些什么鬼话
What on earth are you talking about?
让我解释一下
Let me explain.
你知道的  我是个优秀的遗传变异产物
You see, I'm a superior genetic mutation, uh,
对现有的次品来说存在一个显著提高
An improvement on the existing mediocre stock.
你说的"次品"是什么意思?
And what do you mean, "mediocre stock"?
就是指你
That would be you.
不过在你身体里  有一个潜在的我
But residing within you, is the potential for another me.
一个可能更高  更聪明  雀斑更少的  谢尔顿2.0
Perhaps even taller, smarter, and less prone to freckling, a sheldon 2.0,
可以这么称呼
if you will.
"谢尔顿2.0"?
"sheldon 2.0"?
正是
Exactly.
现在
Now,
我不是说我要专横地决定你要和谁在一起
I am not saying that I should be the sole decider of who you mate with.
如果你不被追求者吸引
If you're not attracted to the suitor,
那怀孕的可能性就会减少
Then the likelihood of conception will be reduced.
你开什么玩笑
You have got to be kidding me.
完全没有
Not at all.
频繁性交会大大增加受精几率
Frequent coitus dramatically increases the odds of fertilization.
好了  谢利  坐下
Okay, shelly, sit down.
我花了一辈子时间去消化这一事实  我的双胞胎哥哥
Now I've lived my whole life dealing with the fact that my twin
像妈妈所说  是个"上帝赐予的特别的小孩"
Brother is, as mom puts it, "one of god's special, little people."
我一直认为我更像一只布谷鸟
I always thought I was more like a cuckoo bird.
你知道的
You know,
一种把蛋放在普通鸟巢里的了不起的生物
A superior creature whose egg is placed in the nest of ordinary birds.
当然  先孵化出的布谷鸟会吃掉所有的食物
Of course, the newly hatched cuckoo eats all the food,
留下其他普通的兄弟姐妹们饿死
Leaving the ordinary siblings to starve to death.
你很幸运  这就是我使用这比喻想要说的
Luckily for you, that's where the metaphor ended.
我还以为你是想说"布谷"
I thought it ended at "cuckoo."
你听好
You listen to me.
如果你想做一个关心妹妹的好哥哥
If you want to start acting like a brother who cares about me,
那太好了
Then terrific.
尽管来做
Bring it on.
但只要你有一次想告诉我该和谁上床
But you try one time to tell me who I should be sleeping with,
我就得跟你回顾回顾
And you and I are going to go round and
我们小时候的那种方式了
Round the way we did when we were little.
没忘吧?
Remember?
-我有另外个提议  -说
I have an alternate proposal. go on.
你捐出卵子
You donate eggs.
我们把它放去低温储藏
We will place them in cryogenic storage.
我会帮你的卵子找一个合格的精子
I will find an appropriate sperm donor for your eggs,
等他们完成受精后再植入你的体内
Have them fertilized and implanted in you.
这样  对每个人都好
That way, everybody wins.
更正下
Correction.
米茜想跟谁约会不关我的事
Missy can date whoever she wants.
我们得想办法解决下
Look, we have to settle this.
我同意
I agree.
谢尔顿的妹妹躲在潘妮家里
Sheldon's sister is hiding at penny's because
是因为我们在同一时间向她发起攻击
We've all been hitting on her at the same time.
她才没躲呢
She's not hiding.
她得留点私人空间来打电话给她生病的奶奶
She needed privacy to call her grandmother who's apparently very sick.
我想她还得洗她的头发
Oh, and then I believe she has to wash her hair.
你这个傻混蛋
Oh, you poor, deluded bastard.
别跟我来劲  你这家伙
Don't start with me, dude.
你还想再来?  来啊
You want to go again? let's go.
-坐下  -好吧
Sit down. okay.
如果我们想争米茜  我们来好好地争
If we're going to fight over missy, let's do it the right way.
有尊严地争
The honorable way.
吃我一拳!
Take that!
还想再来?
You want some more?
他倒下了!
And he's down!
1  2  3
One, two, three...
来啊  快起来啊
Come on, come on! get up!
乖乖躺着吧  婊子
Stay down, bitch!
9  10
...nine, ten.
上帝的选择是正确的
Yeah! natural selection at work.
为人类感到悲哀
I weep for humanity.
失陪  我得去告诉米茜这个好消息
Excuse me while I go tell missy the good news.
-好啊  里奥纳德  -好啊  潘妮
Hey, leonard. oh, hi, penny.
还不错吧
How's it going?
对了  你约会的那个对象麦克  现在还好着吗
Listen, that guy mike that you were dating, is that still going on?
算是吧  怎么了
Uh, pretty much. why?
没事  随便问问
Nothing, just catching up.
顺便  能让我跟米茜说几句吗
By the way, may I speak to missy, please?
当然
Of course.
好啊  里奥纳德  什么事
Hi, leonard. what's up?
你明天就走了
Well, since you're leaving tomorrow,
我想能不能邀你一起吃顿晚饭?
I was wondering if you'd like to go to dinner with me.
你人真好
That's so sweet.
但不用了  谢谢
But no thanks.
你有其它安排还是...?
Oh. do you have other plans or...?
没有
No. oh.
好吧
All right, uh...
祝你今晚过得愉快
Enjoy the rest of your evening.
谢谢  再见
Thanks. see ya.
有点世事难料啊
Um, here's something we didn't anticipate.
有什么能为你效劳的  霍华德?
What do you want, howard?
我很好  多谢关心
I'm fine. thanks for asking.
我来拜访下米茜
I've come to call on missy.
米茜
Missy.
你好  霍华德
Hi, howard.
是神奇的霍华德
The amazing howard.
喜欢魔术吗
Do you like magic?
不喜欢
Not really. no.
那你算是赚到了
Then you are in for a treat.
看好  这是根普通的棍子
Behold, an ordinary cane.
不
No.
好吧
Okay.
米茜
Missy.
谢谢
Thank you.
很感...
I apprec...
感...
Apprec...
感感感...
Appreeee...
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
是不是你的药效退了?
Is your medication wearing off?
你好  开心果
Well, hi, cutie pie.
正想着你会出现呢
I was hoping you'd show up.
我们家养过的一只狗就发这种声音的
We had a dog who made a noise like that.
最后不得不弄死他
Had to put him down.
有什么要我跟妈说的吗
Any news you want me to pass along to mom?
她可能会愿意知道  我已经把研究重点
She might be interested to know that I have refocused my research
从玻色弦论转到了杂交弦论
From bosonic string theory to heterotic string theory.
我就跟她说  你向她问好吧
Yeah, I'll just tell her you say "hey."
很高兴能看到你
Okay, well, it was pleasant seeing you,
除了你对我睾丸干的那事儿
Other than that business with my testicles.
来吧  谢利
Come on, shelly.
我要你知道我很以你为荣
I want you to know I'm very proud of you.
真的?
Really?
当然  我经常跟我朋友们吹嘘我哥哥
Yep, I'm always bragging to my friends about my brother,
是火箭专家(美国人对天才科学家的习惯称呼)
The rocket scientist.
你跟别人说我是火箭专家?
You tell people I'm a rocket scientist?
对啊
Well, yeah.
我是个理论物理学家
I'm a theoretical physicist.
有什么区别
What's the difference?
有什么区别?!
What's the difference?!
我走了  谢利
Good-bye, shelly.
天呐
My god!
你怎么不跟人家说
Why don't you just tell them that
我是金门大桥那儿收通行税的啊?
I'm a toll-taker at the golden gate bridge?!
火箭专家  多丢人啊
Rocket scientist. how humiliating.